A Finding Aid to the Dimitri Hadzi Papers, 1910s-2007, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
Dimitri Hadzi papers
1910s-2007
Archives of American Art
Hadzi, Dimitri, 1921-2006
AAA.hadzdimi
Archival Resource Key
37.2 Linear feet
The papers of Greek American sculptor and educator Dimitri Hadzi measure 37.2 linear feet and date from 1910s-2007, with the bulk of records dating 1936-2007. The collection documents Hadzi's career through biographical material such as education records, World War II files, and some interviews; correspondence with family, artists, art historians, architects, and professional organizations; diaries, notebooks, and other writings; exhibition, gallery and museum, teaching, and project files; personal business records; clippings, exhibition ephemera, invitations, and other printed material; photographs of Hadzi, events and exhibitions, installations, foundries, and studios; some artwork; and audio recordings and motion picture films.
Biographical / Historical
Dimitri Hadzi (1921-2006) was an Greek American sculptor who lived and worked in Rome from the 1950s to 1975, and then in Cambridge, Massachusetts from 1975 to 2006. Born to Greek immigrants, Hadzi attended Brooklyn Technical High School before enlisting in the Army Air Force in 1942. After the World War II, Hadzi studied painting and sculpture at Cooper Union and graduated with honors in 1950. He was awarded a Fulbright fellowship to study at the Polytechnion, Athens, Greece, and subsequently moved to Rome where he remained until the mid-1970s. Hadzi worked mostly with stone and bronze, from which he created semi-abstract shapes and structures drawn from his Greek heritage. His work was selected for the Venice Biennale in 1956, and and his first solo-exhibition came two years later at the Galeria Schneider, Rome, Italy. Throughout his career, Hadzi held solo exhibitions at the Massachusetts Institute of Technology, The Philips Collection, Athens Gallery in Greece, Rikugie Gallery in Japan, and many others. His group exhibitions include Recent Sculptor USA (1959), Museum of Modern Art, New York; Annual Exhibition, The Whitney Museum (1961); Seven Sculptors at Harvard, Harvard University (1983); and American Academy of Arts & Letters Centennial Portfolio, Pace Prints, New York (1998). Hadzi's public commissions include those at the Massachusetts Institute of Technology (1963), St. Paul's Church, Rome, Italy (1966-1976), Dallas Center, Texas (1980). His artwork is held in permanent collections of the Hirshhorn Museum and Scultpure Garden, Solomon R. Guggenheim Museum, Hakone Museum of Sculpture in Japan, and the Montreal Museum of Art, among others. Hadzi was professor of Visual and Environmental Studies at Harvard University from 1975-1989, and was named Professor Emeritus in 1989.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged as 13 series.
Series 1: Biographical Material, 1910s, bulk 1936-2004 (Box 1-3, 33; 2.7 linear feet)
Series 2: Correspondence, 1943-2007 (Box 3-6; 3 linear feet)
Series 3: Diaries and Notebooks, 1939-2006 (Box 6-9; 3 linear feet)
Series 4: Writing Files, 1945-2003 (Box 9; 10 folders)
Series 5: Exhibition Files, 1958-2002 (Box 9-10; 1.2 linear feet)
Series 6: Project Files, 1957-2002 (Box 11-15, 33; 4.7 linear feet)
Series 7: Teaching Files, 1955-2000 (Box 15-16; 12 folders)
Series 8: Museum and Gallery Files, 1947-2008 (Box 16-17; 1.8 linear feet)
Series 9: Personal Business Records, 1949-2007 (Box 17-20; 2.5 linear feet)
Series 10: Printed Material, 1949-2007 (Box 20-24, 33; 3.7 linear feet)
Series 11: Photographs, circa 1930s-2006 (Box 24-25, 33; 1.5 linear feet)
Series 12: Artwork, circa 1939-1998 (Box 25; 11 folders)
Series 13: Audiovisual Material (Box 26-40; 11.1 linear feet)
Scope and Contents
The papers of Greek American sculptor and educator Dimitri Hadzi measure 37.2 linear feet and date from 1910s-2007, with the bulk of records dating 1936-2007. The collection documents Hadzi's career through biographical material; correspondence; diaries, notebooks, and other writings; exhibition, gallery and museum, teaching, and project files; personal business records; printed material; photographs, some artwork, audio recordings, and motion picture films.
Biographical material includes files pertaining to Hadzi's education at Cooper Union (1946-1950) and Polytechnion in Athens, Greece (1950-1951) as well as his high school years at Brooklyn Technical High School (1936-1940); years enlisted in the Army Air Force (1942-1946); and his hobbies of music, mineral collecting, and geology. Also found are address books, honors and awards, interviews, and resumes. Hadzi's professional correspondents include artists, art historians, architects, and professional organizations. Also found is personal correspondence with family, friends, and acquaintances, most extensively during his years in the military.
Diaries and notebooks consist of memoranda books, travel logs, and annotated calendars. Writings include drafts, correspondence, and some printed material from Dimitri Hadzi (1996) by Peter Selz. Material gathered for his incomplete memoir, artist statements, and writings about Hadzi are also present.
Exhibition files shed light on various group and solo exhibitions of Hadzi's work. The files mostly consist of shipping records, correspondence, press releases and other printed matter, photographs, and loan documents. Gallery and museum files include loan and sale agreements, price lists, clippings, newsletters, shipping information, and some papers related to exhibitions.
Project files include sketches and blueprints, correspondence, legal documents, shipping information, and some audiovisual material regarding the installation of Hadzi's sculptures. The files also pertain to recasted sculptures, small-scale projects, and unexecuted commissions. Teaching Files include administrative correspondence, clippings, lecture and discussion notes, course descriptions, and correspondence from Hadzi's tenure as Visual and Environmental Studies professor at Harvard University. Papers related to instructor positions, employment opportunities, and lectures outside of Harvard are also present. Personal business records include sales, inventories, and other financial material; correspondence, shipping information, and price lists from foundries and material distributors; studio logs, correspondence, and notes.
Printed materials consist of exhibition invitations, announcements, post cards, and books; news clippings and articles; printed matter from special events, exhibitions of other artists, press releases, and newsletters. Photographs include portraits and snapshots of Hadzi, depicting him working in studios and foundries, at installation sites and events, and with his family. Also included are photographs of other artists, Hadzi's travel in Japan, and his artwork. Artwork found in this collection consists of six sketchbooks, several small drawings, and one woodblock.
Audiovisual material is extensive and includes documentation of the creation, installation, and exhibition of some of Hadzi's work. The majority of the footage centers on the creation and installation of the Thermopylae sculpture in front of the JFK Federal Building in Boston, Massachusetts in 1968.
Conditions Governing Access
The collection is open for research. Archival audiovisual recordings must be digitized for research access. Researchers may access digitized audiovisual materials in the Archives' Washington, D.C. or New York, N.Y. Research Centers by appointment. Contact Reference Services for more information.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated 1989 and 1998 by Dimitri Hadzi and in 2008 and 2011 by Cynthia Hadzi, Dimitri Hadzi's widow.
Sculpture, Modern -- 20th century; World War, 1939-1945; Drawings; Interviews; Sound recordings; Video recordings; Educators -- Massachusetts -- Cambridge; Sculptors -- Italy -- Rome; Sculptors -- Massachusetts -- Cambridge; Diaries; Motion picture film; Foundry, Nicci; Harvard University -- Faculty
- Biographical Material, 1910s, bulk 1936-2004; Series 1; Archival Resource Key; 2.7 Linear feet Box 1-3, 33
  Scope and Contents
  The files consist of address books, travel ephemera, identification cards and passports, honors and awards, several editions of Hadzi's curriculum vitae, and some interviews. Course notebooks, notes, certificates and some photographs papers document Hadzi's education at Brooklyn Technical High School (1936-1940), Cooper Union (1946-1950), and the Polytechnion in Athens, Greece (1950-1951). World War II files include photographs, printed materials, applications, reports, and memos from his time enlisted in the Army Air Force. Ephemera related to Hadzi's interest in geology, mineral collecting, and music can also be found in this series.
  - Address Books, circa 1940s-1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 1-4)
  - Baptism Record; Vaccination Certificate, 1927, 1949; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Curricula Vitae, circa 1950-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Education, P.S. 100; Brooklyn Technical High School, 1931-1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Education, Assignment Book, circa 1936-1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Education, Course Notebook, American History, circa 1936-1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Education, Course Notebook, Chemistry, 1936-1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 10-14)
  - Education, Course Notebook, English, 1939-1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Education, Course Notebook, Industrial Processes, 1935-1936; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 16-17)
  - Education, Course Notebooks, Power Generation and Distribution, 1939; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Education, Course Notebooks, Quantitative Chemical Analysis, circa 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Education, Course Notebook, Shop Notes, circa 1936-1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Education, Notebook, circa 1936-1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Education, Miscellaneous Course Material, circa 1936-1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Education, Cooper Union; Brooklyn Museum Art School, 1946-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 1-5)
  - Education, G. I. Bill, 1948-1954; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Education, Fulbright Scholarship; Polytechnion, Athens, Greece, 1949-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Education, Cooper Union, Greece, Rome, Photographs, 1946-1954; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 8-9)
  - Education, Courses Taken, Sushi, 1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Honors and Awards, American Academy of Arts and Sciences, Certificate and Photographs, 1978, 1992-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Honors and Awards, American Institute of Architects; Boston Society of Architects, 1975-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Honors and Awards, Greek Institute, 1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Honors and Awards, Krautheimer, 1977-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Honors and Awards, Lawrence University, 1986-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 14-15)
  - Honors and Awards, Miscellaneous, 1953-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Honors and Awards, Miscellaneous, Photographs, circa 1970s-1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Identification Cards and Passports, 1939-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 18-19)
  - Interview with Manson Kennedy, 1974 July; Archival Resource Key; 2 Sound cassettes (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Interview with Elena Spiloti, 1997; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound cassette (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Interview Transcript, Silvia, 1980 March 24; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Interview Transcript, Robert Brown, Archives of American Art, 1990; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 23-24)
  - Interview Transcript, Chris Busa, 2000 December 17; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Interview Questionnaire, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Interchemical Corp., New York City, 1940-1941; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Luncheon Concert, 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Mineral Collecting; Geology, 1971-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Papers of Dimitri Hadzi, Archives of American Art; AAA Membership, 1975-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Papers, General, circa 1918-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Retirement Plan, "Operazione Liberazione", circa 1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Travel Ephemera, circa 1950-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - World War II, Papers, 1942-1949; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 8-10)
  - World War II, Photographs, circa 1942-1946; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 11-13)
- Correspondence, 1943-2007; Series 2; Archival Resource Key; 3 Linear feet Box 3-6
  Hadzi's correspondents include architects, art historians, professional organizations, artists, collectors, and family members. The files contain some printed material, legal documents, and personal business records as well. Hadzi's military correspondence is with relatives and friends; it was during his time enlisted in the Army Air Force that his interest in drawing blossomed. Also present is one folder of letters that belonged to Dimitri's brother, Thomas Hadzi.
  - Architects, Max Abramovitz, 1960-1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Architects, The Architects Collaborative and Samuel Glaser Associates, 1965-1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Architects, Gropius, Walter, 1963-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Architects, Skidmore, Owings, and Merrill, 1962-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Architects, Miscellaneous, 1955-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 18-19)
  - Art Historians and Critics, MacDonald, William L., 1958-1987; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Art Historians and Critics, Millon, Henry, 1960-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Art Historians and Critics, Norland, Gerald, 1988-1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Art Historians and Critics, A-Z, 1956-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 23-24)
  - Artists, Frank Monaco, 1954-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Artists, B-Z, 1941-2007; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 2-6)
  - Artists, General, 1951-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Collectors, David Rockefeller, 1966-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Collectors, 1955-2005; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 9-10)
  - Fan Mail, 1981-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - General, 1938-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 12-18)
  - General, 1990-2009, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 1-2)
  - Last Name, A-Z, 1949-1988; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 3-8)
  - Media and Publishing, 1955-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Military, 1943-1945; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 10-16)
  - Military, 1945-1946; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 1-3)
  - Organizations, American Academy and Institute of Arts and Letters, 1962, 1987-1996; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Organizations, Art, 1962-1992; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Organizations, Asian Arts Council, 1984-1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Organizations, International Sculpture Conference, 1978-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Organizations, Museum of Fine Arts, Boston, 1989-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Organizations, Miscellaneous, 1939-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Thomas Hadzi, 1943-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Diaries and Notebooks, 1939-2006; Series 3; Archival Resource Key; 3 Linear feet Box 6-9
  Annotated calendars, daily notebooks, memoranda books, travel logs, and some loose notes; several journals containing longer and more reflective entries by Hadzi; one notebook from Hadzi's time in the Pacific towards the end of World War II; and two notebooks titled "Etching and Engraving."
  - Annotated Desk Calendars, 1962-2001; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 11-18)
  - Daily Notebooks, 1970s-1980s; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Daily Notebooks, 1980-2005, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 1-4)
  - Diary, 1939-2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 5-14)
  - Etching and Engraving, Notes and Records, 1970-1994; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Etching and Engraving, Lapidary, circa 1994-1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Journal, circa 1955-1986; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 17-19)
  - Memoranda Books, 1951-1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 20-24)
  - Memoranda Books, 1960-2004; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 1-24)
  - Notebook, World War II, 1942-1946; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Notebook, German and Italian Language, circa 1950-1970s; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Notebook, "Dreamworld", 1972, 2006; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Notes, Miscellaneous, circa 1950-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 28-29)
  - Travel Log, 1973-1998; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 1-11)
  - Travel Log, Transcribed Fragments, 1944-1989; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Travel, Loose Notes, 1956, 1991; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Writing Files, 1945-2003; Series 4; Archival Resource Key; 10 Folders Box 9
  A few folders contain drafts, correspondence, press releases, clippings, and other papers related to Dimitri Hadzi (1996) by Peter Selz. Papers compiled for Hadzi's incomplete memoir include letters, notes, printed material, and other ephemera that date back to the mid-1940s. Also present are some artist statements and writings about Hadzi and his work.
  - Hadzi Memoir and Writings, 1945-2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 14-15)
  - Hadzi Memoir and Writings; "Brooklyn in the 30s", 1951-2003; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Monograph, Dimitri Hadzi (1996), 1978, 1995-1997; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 16-17)
  - Book Thank You Letters, 1997-1999; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Hadzi Statements and Writings, circa 1980s-1990s; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 19-20)
  - Papers and Other Writings on Hadzi, 1956-2000; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Hadzi as Poetic Inspiration for Others, circa 1980-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Exhibition Files, 1958-2002; Series 5; Archival Resource Key; 1.2 Linear feet Box 9-10
  Exhibition files document group and solo exhibitions containing Hadzi's work. Folders may contain correspondence, clippings and press releases, photographs, loan agreements, and shipping details. Also found in this series are several countdown calendars and 11 exhibition guest books.
  - Pittsburgh International Exhibition of Contemporary Painting and Sculpture (1958; 1964; 1967), Carnegie Institute, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1958-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - International Small Bronze Sculpture Competitions and Exhibitions, 1959-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Plastik (1962), Galerie Hella Neblung, Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Dimitri Hadzi: Sculptures (1963), Massachusetts Institute of Technology, Cambridge, Massachusetts, Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Dimitri Hadzi: Sculptures (1963), Massachusetts Institute of Technology, Cambridge, Massachusetts, Guest Book, Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - White House Festival of the Arts (1965), 1965, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Dimitri Hadzi Sculpture: 15 Years in Rome, 1953-1968 (1968-1969), Tyler School of Art, Rome, Italy, Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Dimitri Hadzi Sculpture: 15 Years in Rome, 1953-1968 (1968-1969), Tyler School of Art, Rome, Italy, Guest Book, Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - American Artists in Rome (1968; 1969), United States Information Service, Italy, 1968-1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Prints from the Collection of Dimitri Hadzi (1978), The Arts Club of Chicago, Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Art in the Vice Presidents House (1979), Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Europalia (1982), Brussels, Belgium, Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Dimitri Hadzi: Pillars of Hercules and Related Works (1983), Fogg Art Museum, Cambridge, Massachusetts, Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Bronze at Washington Square (1984) Public Art Trust, Washington, D.C., 1983-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - The Fifth Henry Moore Prize Exhibition (1987), The Hakone Open Air Museum, Japan, Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Outdoor Sculpture: Dimitri Hadzi (1991), Phillips Collection, Washington, D.C., 1990-1993; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Modern Odysseys: Greek American Artists of the 20th Century (2002), Queens Museum of Art, New York, Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence and Papers, 1956-1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Countdown Calendars, 1961-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Guest Book, Unidentified Exhibitions, 1958, 1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Guest Book, Private Exhibition at Helene Seiferheld's Apartment, 1959; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Guest Book, Stephen Radich Gallery, 1961-1962; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Guest Book, Hopkins Center, New Hampshire, 1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Guest Book, Felix Landau Gallery, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Guest Book, Richard Gray Gallery, 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Guest Book, Obelisco Gallery, 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Guest Book, Gruenbaum Gallery; Studio Sign-in Book, circa 1978-1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 22-23)
  - Guest Book, Unidentified Exhibition, 1995; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Guest Book, Unidentified Exhibition, 2002; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Guest Book, Alpha Gallery, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Project Files, 1957-2002; Series 6; Archival Resource Key; 4.7 Linear feet Box 11-15
  Project files include correspondence, sketches and blueprints, architectural plans, legal documents, photographs, printed material, and some audiovisual material. Several folders relate to Hadzi's projects as set designer and book illustrator.
  Arrangement
  This series is divided into two sub-series. Selected Public Commissions include Hadzi's more well-known outdoor sculptures, while Other Commissions and Projects consist of recasted sculpture installations, unexecuted projects, and Hadzi's less-known endeavors.
  - Selected Public Commissions, 6.1; Archival Resource Key
    Files include correspondence with architects, companies, municipalities, and organizations that commissioned Hadzi; printed material such as press releases, clippings, and books; some photographs of sites, models, installations, and events; legal documents; and some audio recordings. Almost all of Hadzi's sculptures from this series were installed in the United States, one exception being Hadzi's Bronze Doors, commissioned by the St. Paul Within-the-Walls church in Rome, Italy.
    - Elmo (1963), Massachusetts Institute of Technology, Cambridge, MA, 1962-1963; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Helios (1965), Sun Life Insurance Company, Baltimore, Maryland, 1963-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 2-4)